Cherry：Do we wait here?
Cherry：在這裡等嗎？
Xenon：Yes. Why did you accompany me here anyway?
Xenon：嗯，是說妳到底為什麼也跟來了？
Cherry：Hey, I took part in the Boss fight; make sense that I get to rescue the princess, right? I want to see NEKO in person as well.
Cherry：我都打過 Boss 了，沒救到公主不是很奇怪嗎？我也想看看 NEKO 嘛。
Xenon：... Princess? I say more pixie than princess.
Xenon：……什麼公主啊？是妖精吧。
Cherry：You are so mean~ She's a cute girl. isn't she?
Cherry：好壞喔，是個可愛的女孩子不是嗎？
Xenon：Umm... She's... unique, to say the least. Be prepared when you see her.
Xenon：呃……總之是個古怪的傢伙，妳要有心理準備。
Cherry：All this talk is making me even more interested to see her!
Cherry：那我更想看了！
Cherry：On a side note, that's a serious crowd down there at the main entrance.
Cherry：話說剛剛看到樓下大門超多人的耶。
Cherry：Good thing you had friends that could let us in through the back door. I thought we're gonna get stuck outside.
Cherry：好險有你朋友帶我們走後門，我還以為進不來了。
Cherry：Didn't you say that the admins have been watching you closely?
Cherry：你不是說你被管理局盯得很緊嗎？
Xenon：I still have my connections over here. If not, I wouldn't know any of this in the first place.
Xenon：我在這還是有一些人脈，不然我也不會知道這些。
Cherry：Wow, so a shut-in like you actually made "friends"...
Cherry：你這自閉兒居然也能交到朋友啊……
Xenon：You... it's all thanks to them that the evidence I provided could actually influence the investigation.
Xenon：喂……幸虧有他們，才能拿我給的證據轉移調查方向
Xenon：... Ah, we should stop chatting here.
Xenon：……啊、別在這裡聊了。
[>>>Fast Forward>>>]
[>>>快轉>>>]
Xenon：Hey. Over here.
Xenon：喂，這裡。
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Ehhh? Why are you the one to come and get me? Where are my dad and others?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：欸欸？為什麼是你來接我？我爸他們呢？
Xenon： I notify them to wait at home. There are still some procedures to go through.
Xenon：我通知他們在家等了，還有一些手續要辦
Xenon：You probably have no idea why you are released, right?
Xenon：妳應該還搞不清楚為什麼會被釋放吧？
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Dude, I don't even know why I was arrested in the first place! It's utterly ridiculous!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：我連為什麼被抓起來都搞不清楚啊！ 簡直莫名奇妙！
Xenon：You don't remember, do you...? That makes it even harder to explain things clearly.
Xenon：不記得了嗎……？那可能更難解釋了。
NEKO#ΦωΦ：...... Who's that behind you?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：……後面那是？
Cherry：Hi~
Cherry：嗨～
NEKO#ΦωΦ：EHHH!? It's Cherry! OH MY ****** GOD!!!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：欸！？是 Cherry 啊！哇哇哇！！
Cherry：Eh? You recognize me?
Cherry：咦？妳知道我？
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Of course! NEKO is a big fan of yours! Why are you here!?
NEKO#ΦωΦ：NEKO 是妳的大粉啊！妳怎麼會在這裡！？
Xenon：She's half the reason why you could be released.
Xenon：妳能出來有一半是她的功勞。
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Huh? What does that mean? Hmm??
NEKO#ΦωΦ：咦？什麼意思？咦？？
Xenon：It's a long story... All in all, we should leave here before we get any attention. Let's go.
Xenon：說來話長……總之趁沒引起騷動前快出去吧，走。
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Come on~ tell me what's going on~
NEKO#ΦωΦ：吼～～解釋一下啦！
Xenon：You are so noisy... I'll tell you once we leave here.
Xenon：吵死了……路上再慢慢說啦。
Xenon：There's a **** ton of people at the main entrance ready to engulf you. Keep your head down.
Xenon：大門一堆人在堵妳，低調一點。
[Signal Lost]
[訊號中斷]